Md Faisal Hossain

Bangladesh



hello.faisalhossain@outlook.com



01814366774



linkedin.com/in/mdfaisalhossain1



https://faisalhossain1.github.io/profile/

Summary

Hi, This is Faisal. I am a Web Developer & I am from Bangladesh. Experienced Data Entry Operator with a demonstrated history of working in the government administration industry. Skilled in Python (programming Language), C# (Programming Language), HTML(Hyper Text Markup Language), CSS (Cascading Style Sheets), JavaScript, Bootstrap(framework), React (framework), Node Js, Github, Unity (game engine), Filmora X, logo Making, video editing & Microsoft office.

Experience



fi Web Developer

Fiverr

Dec 2020 - Present (10 months +)

Youtube Content Creator

YouTube

Dec 2020 - Present (10 months +)

• Develop original content through social listening and independent sources.

Data Entry Operator

Income Tax Department, UK

Mar 2020 - Present (1 year 7 months +)

- Maintained databases, mailing lists, telephone networks, and other information to facilitate functioning of health education programs.
- Compiled [Timeframe] budget reports, financial spreadsheets and organizational charts to support business operations and improve office organization.

Education



Adarsha Pre-Cadet School

SSC

2020 - 2022

Skills

Python (Programming Language) • JavaScript • GitHub • Video Editing • Html • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap • React.js • Node js • Microsoft Office